LX Jordon Bobo

(801) 386-3402 github.com/JordonBobo jordon.bobo@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/jordon-bobo/

Qualifications Summary:

2 years of experience developing and maintaining computer scripts. Strong analytic skills that made it possible to adhere to federal compliance standards in systems with protected information. Currently involved in a full-stack education program with the University of Utah.

Skills and Languages:

JavaScriptMySQLHTML/CSSDiligentNode.JSProblem SolvingTeam-PlayerAnalyticalDetail Oriented

Professional Experience:

Utah Higher Education Assistance Authority (UHEAA):

Systems Support Specialist (May 2019 – February 2021)

- Extensive multitasking in order to complete overlapping projects and tasks without overlooking any key system or variable.
- Fostered a collaboration-focused environment to develop, maintain, and improve in-house software.

Processor (Jan. 2018-May 2019)

• Exceeded all expected accomplishment standards by more than 20% with the lowest number of quality assurance issues in the department.

Murray City Corporation:

Library Services Aide (November 2013 – July 2017)

- Facilitated the library's acquisition and implementation of new ILS software and Self-Service Machines.
- Administered meetings which concluded how to best utilize \$50,000+ annual capital expenditures budget.

Arborist Assistant (May 2013 – November 2013)

The International Plutarch Society:

Academic Secretary (January 2013 – May 2013)

- Utilized information technologies to modernize 300+ documents for archival purposes.
- Used Visual Basic to modify Excel spreadsheets and generate new documents.

Education:

University of Utah Coding Bootcamp (November 2020 - May 2021)

Intensive training program to gain exposure to full-stack programming.

Utah State University. (Graduated May 2013)

Bachelor of Arts in History.